<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>We Love West Michigan. on Citizen Labs</title>
    <link>https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in We Love West Michigan. on Citizen Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/join_us/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/join_us/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Respect Citizen Labs is an intentionally positive community: that recognizes and celebrates creativity; collaboration of independent creators (and independence); and the diversity of people, cultures, and opinions that are a core strength of Citizen Labs.
Citizen Labs spaces are an inclusive environment, based on treating all individuals respectfully, regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, age, disability, medical conditions, nationality, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), physical appearance, or technology preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citizenlabsgr.github.io/homepage-v2/contact/</guid>
      <description>Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   
Where To Find Us On Hacknights On the first and third Tuesday of every month we meet for a Hacknight, a chance to build, share and learn about tools to create, support, and serve the public good. To learn more and RSVP for an upcoming Hacknight please visit our Meetup page.
Hacknights take place at The Factory, at 6pm on the fourth floor above the San Chez restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>