<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>We Love Our City. on Citizen Labs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in We Love Our City. on Citizen Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday: Citizen Labs</title>
      <link>/post/2018-04-17_happy_birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-04-17_happy_birthday/</guid>
      <description>Citizen Labs has much to celebrate! It was just one year ago when our application to become 501c3 nonprofit was approved. We have seen tremendous growth as measured by budget, hack night involvement, organization, community feedback, and partnerships.
By The Numbers  102 Slack members 41 Active Slack users 172 Meetup members 219 Facebook followers 4 Deployed Projects  Accomplishments January - March: Our efforts were heavily focused on creating the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FY2018 Budget Added to Open Budget: GR</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-02_open_budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-02_open_budget/</guid>
      <description>Interested in the City of Grand Rapids&amp;rsquo; budget, but don&amp;rsquo;t have time to thumb through the 326 page document? A great place to start in learning more about the nearly $530 Million budget is by visiting Open Budget: Grand Rapids.
What&amp;rsquo;s New?  Open Budget: Grand Rapids now includes the FY2018 budget information that was approved by the City Council in June 2017.
 An interactive timeline of the budget process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Opportunities</title>
      <link>/post/2018-01-24_priorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-01-24_priorities/</guid>
      <description>2017 was an exciting year for Citizen Labs. We grew as an organization, spending a great deal of energy in creating a strong foundation that can deliver on our mission.
We have set bold goals to deliver on our mission.
Citizen Labs works together with our entire community to promote transparency, better understand problems, and support informed decisions.   And to be purposeful in choosing the opportunities that may cross our path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Citizen Labs</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Citizen Labs works together with our entire community to promote transparency, better understand problems, and support informed decisions. We apply open data and open source technology, convene civic volunteers, and engage community leadership to create data-driven solutions.
Our volunteer community runs and drives all Citizen Labs projects! We highly encourage all to become involved and contribute. We believe from our neighborhoods to our cities there&amp;rsquo;s always more room for improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Respect Citizen Labs is an intentionally positive community: that recognizes and celebrates creativity; collaboration of independent creators (and independence); and the diversity of people, cultures, and opinions that are a core strength of Citizen Labs.
Citizen Labs spaces are an inclusive environment, based on treating all individuals respectfully, regardless of gender identity, sexual orientation, age, disability, medical conditions, nationality, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), physical appearance, or technology preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   
Where To Find Us On Hacknights On the first and third Tuesday of every month we meet for a Hacknight, a chance to build, share and learn about tools to create, support, and serve the public good. To learn more and RSVP for an upcoming Hacknight please visit our Meetup page.
Hacknights take place at The Factory, at 6pm on the fourth floor above the San Chez restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>/join_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/join_us/</guid>
      <description>What We Do We ask questions. We experiment and sometimes fail, but understand that learning cannot happen without failure. We apply what we learn and work to always make improvements.
We come together in-person to share successes, seek support, and work on individual and group projects. When we are not together in-person, we work together online. Citizen Labs has a Code of Conduct that applies to all of our activities, events, and digital forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Work</title>
      <link>/our_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our_work/</guid>
      <description> How We Do It We use modern tools and practices to improve how decisions are made and services delivered. We use the following guidelines when working on projects:
 Design with users, not for them Invite participation and work in the open Use data to drive decisions Start small and continuously improve  View projects by status: Active Development | Live | Discovery
Projects Under Active Development  Projects that are Live  Projects in Discovery Phase  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>